One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Arrival of the Mysterious Man and
the News Coo!
The gas didn't work at all?!
This protective suit was made by Vegapunk, and in fact...
...it's way beyond Caesar's ability.
Caesar knew that, that's why...
All of you, just run!
The protective suit won't help!
Take it off and run to the lab now!
And that's how they all got petrified.
--Let's get going!
--Yeah!
Those who got petrified are still alive!
They're just in a state of apparent death
paralyzed in the shell.
Yeah, but after half a day,
the poison will spread and kill them.
We have to find them
and break the shell before that!
Thank you...
...for allowing us to enter the island.
I'll never forget your name.
I can save my people's lives!
I promise I'll come
back to turn myself in!
This is the only exit anyway.
Just go!
Okay!
What should we do with these?
Are they pirates?
I don't know. It's just creepy.
Isn't that somebody's head?!
Huh? Don't be ridiculous!
Y-You were right!
Heads are...
flying toward us!
That guy is...
D-Doflamingo!
Why is he here?!
The Conqueror's Haki!?
Why did you do that?!
They're not here.
The ship is gone.
You're a Warlord!
Why are you attacking the Navy?!
I know some pirates were
here little while ago.
Where did they go?
How dare you do that to our colleagues!
Don't do it!
I can't move my fingers.
Law is different...
but Straw Hat is just an ordinary pirate.
Don't!
Where did they go, you bastards?!
Stop messing with my soldiers!
Tell me where those shitheads went.
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
Well, I don't know,
Joker.
We could've caught them
but we let them get away.
So they're gone then!?
But you... I think you know too much.
Smo-yan!
Vice Admiral Smo!!
No, Brook! It's not a "little lamb"!
It's the Mini-Merry #2!
You're the eighth person to ask me that.
Like I told the rest,
I got out to the sea through
a channel in the lab
and retrieved the Mini-Merry #2.
which had been docked
at the entrance to the island.
I see, I see.
So that little lamb
was okay. That's good!
Nami, where are we going next?
Hold on.
The next destination is already set.
It's Dressrosa.
D-Dressrosa?!
Do you know the place?
Th-That's exactly where we...
I mean, I want to go!
You need to go there, too?!
Uh-huh, I think so!
The current is shifting?!
A slope?!
Yee-ha!
It's fast! The ship's going fast!
Look out for rock reefs!
It's a sea slope. It's not uncommon.
It is uncommon!
We don't have to go against the current.
The needle in the middle
on your Log Pose must be
pointing toward Dressrosa.
But don't try to go straight.
Take a detour.
Come to think of it,
you were talking on the Transponder Snail earlier.
Who were you talking to?
That was Doflamingo.
Doflamingo?! The Warlord?!
I've heard he's the most evil one!
The plan is already in action.
What plan?
Yeah, tell us about the plan!
Get together, everybody!
We formed an alliance
to take down one of the Four Emperors?!
The Four Emperors, huh?
It's great!
No, it's not!
Wait, wait! Let's calm down, everybody!
Luffy, tell them about the alliance.
Okay! We and Tra-guy's pirate group
formed an alliance!
Let's be nice to each other!
Does anybody wanna oppose this?!
--I do!
Does it make any difference?
Luffy's mind is already set, isn't it?
Thank you.
But I have to warn you.
There may be a slight difference between
how you define "alliance" and how Luffy defines it.
Be careful.
That's why Luffy kept saying "kidnap"...
which was so out of character for him.
If he had just come to me
with that strange sheep
and asked me to cook it, I
wouldn't know what to do.
You bastards.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Extraordinarily big names
will hunt you down!
Idiots!
Realize how stupid you are! Go to hell!
Hey, Sanji! I was in the
middle of his treatment!
Wait until I finish it.
Really?!
I asked you guys to kidnap
Caesar at Punk Hazard.
Meanwhile, I destroyed
the machine which was
manufacturing a substance called SAD.
The great pirates in the New World
often have their own territory.
They lead countless numbers of people
and reign like a syndicate.
It's nothing like what
you've seen before.
One pirate group is never strong enough
even to see their captain's face.
But since it's an underground community,
they have to do their businesses secretly
to avoid the Navy.
And Doflamingo is the most trusted
and powerful man among them.
His underground alias is Joker.
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
...one of the Four Emperors,
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
Our target.
What?! K-Kaido?!
Kaido?!
What's the matter?
Never mind. Go on.
Why is there a dragon here?!
Where did Momonosuke go?!
That's him.
Kaido of the Four Emperors.
In order to take him down,
we have to weaken his forces.
Kaido is buying a large amount
of fruit from Joker now.
It's a Zoan-type, man-made,
devil fruit called SMILE.
M-Man-made?!
If such a thing exists,
the number of devil fruit
eaters will keep multiplying!
That's right.
Since it's man-made, however,
it seems like there are some risks involved.
But, in fact, Kaido has
more than 500 devil fruit
eaters in his pirate group.
Who doesn't wanna do this?! I don't!
--I don't!
Shut up.
But the devil fruit eaters
won't multiply anymore.
Really? Him?
Were you making a substance
for the man-made devil fruit?
How cool! SAD!
Don't praise him!
He just put Vegapunk's discovery
of "lineage factor" into practice.
So Vegapunk is the smart one.
Shut up, you bastards!
Can you fools even make it?!
Joker is finished.
We're gonna go onto the next move.
There is a factory manufacturing SMILEs
somewhere on Dressrosa.
We should just find it and destroy it?
That's right.
However, he's a professional
businessman.
I'm sure he'll retaliate.
Is that where you wanna go, Kin?
Indeed!
A comrade of mine is captured there!
Huh!?
--Stop it, please!
--Smo-yan's gonna die!
If you kill him,
who would lead misfits like us!?
Don't worry.
There is no way to find
out who knows what.
That's why, Law,
Straw Hat, and you soldiers,
I'm gonna kill you all!
Stop!
Whoa-whoa.
Excuse me, young man.
Could you step aside?
What!?
He is my...
friend.
Is that the former admiral - Aokiji?!
Young Master!
Young Master-sama!
T-Thank god-dasuyan!
He didn't get frozen to the bone!
Young Master-sama!
Smo-yan!
I'm not interested in fighting you.
But if I can't silence that guy,
I have to change my plan.
Can I ask you something?
You, now...
where do you stand, Kuzan?!
Your reputation is sullied.
Hey, treat him already!
Y-Yes, sir!
The face of a mere wanderer...
and that of a man with determination...
they're quite different.
I never thought that the World
Government was almighty.
There are things I can do
without belonging to the Navy.
There are things I can see now
because I'm not part of the Navy.
I was dead for a moment.
Maybe I was fated to come here.
What brought you here?
I came here to see you.
How did you know that I'd be here?
Don't tell me...
you have something to do with
the underground community now?
T-The former admiral has
something to do with...
If you're done with the
treatment, go away!
I'm still me, Smoker.
Then I have no qualms.
Anyway, you guys should
keep an eye on Doflamingo.
He's a Warlord and the
king of Dressrosa.
He's an unusual pirate in many ways
but not like the Snake Princess of the Kuja.
Tell Sakazuki to get the
admirals into action.
In the worst-case scenario,
things could go very wrong, very quickly,
and it would become the most
serious matter Sakazuki faced
since taking over Navy HQ.
I've warned you.
Hey, guys!
You have to keep this...
I mean... you know.
What was it?
I forgot. Who cares.
It's a secret that we met you, got it!
That night, out at sea
It's already late! No one has come!
Yes, sir! I didn't see anybody!
Uh-huh. Good job!
Thank you, sir!
Hey, do you think they
can still find us?
How many people are looking for us?!
Tens of thousands?
I can't stop worrying
since I heard you blackmailed Doflamingo!
Me, neither, you fool!
Kin gave us armor and some helmets.
Just let it go!
Resign from the Warlords
or fight one of the Emperors.
Nobody can choose between those options.
He'll just come to kill us.
I'm scared!
You bastard! Fight me squarely!
Stop!
I said it's a long story!
--Cut it out!
--Stop!
Come on! It's dangerous
to fight on the ship!
Oh, are you playing samurai?!
Fight, fight!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
The whole country was left heartbroken!
The grave of the Wano Kingdom's hero,
left plundered by a thief!
That was you!
I said I didn't do it!
You must have! You have
that legendary swordsman...
Ryuma's great sword Shusui on your belt!
Come on, come on! Fight, fight!
Just cut him already!
Who wants to eat a midnight snack?
Oh! What is it?!
Pizza.
"Pida"?
I don't know what that is
but if he cooked it, it should be good.
Did Momonosuke go to bed already?
He's taking a bath with Robin.
What?!
You haven't taken a bath
for days, have you?
Nope.
Did you get all warmed up?
Uh-huh. Not bad.
You came at just the right time!
Kin'emon-san, he needs a kimono.
What are you doing, you dirty brat!
It's not fair!
You're taking full advantage
of being a child!
Just cut off your top-knot!
Hey! Why did you gang up on a child?!
N-No, it's not what you think, Nami-san!
M-Men are all...
I was scared, beautiful princess!
Beautiful princess?!
Don't be so honest!
You're such a lovely boy!
You sleep in our room, Momo-chan!
What?!
They'll let him in the girls'
room - the secret garden?!
What?!
You're the worst, you brat!
Doflamingo! I know he's gonna make a raid in the darkness of the night!
Just bring it on! I mean, don't!
I-I can't sleep!
Calm all the way to the horizon!
The morning paper!
"Donquixote Doflamingo..."
"as a Warlord..."
"has resigned"!
"And abdicates the throne of Dressrosa"!?
What the hell!?
T-"Throne" means he was a king?!
A king?!
Then it must be a birds' kingdom!
When things go this well,
it's kind of scary.
This is good. He had no choice.
By the way, why are our
faces here as well?
"The Warlord - Trafalgar Law..."
"Forms an unusual alliance
with the Straw Hats"?
"It is still unknown what the
Government will do to Law." It says!
There's so much going
on in today's paper!
Various places in the world
Doflamingo quits the Warlords and
Law and Straw Hat join forces!
And these guys, too!
Captain Kid!
Scratchmen Apoo!
Basil Hawkins!
The Kid Pirates, the On Air Pirates,
and the Hawkins Pirates have
formed a pirate alliance, too?!
They were the troublemakers...
that everyone kept an eye
on for last two years...
and now they've joined
forces all at once!
Is something about to
happen in the New World?!
They formed an alliance, too, huh?
I wonder if they're thinking
the same thing as us.
Forget about them.
We're gonna go on with the plan.
Focus on Doflamingo for now.
Now you know how important yesterday's
negotiation was for him.
All we did was kidnap Caesar.
In contrast, seemingly overnight, he gave up...
his throne which he's had for ten years...
and the carte blanche given to him
as a privilege of being a Warlord.
He did it just to get this
guy back and that says a lot!
Dressrosa.
In response to Doflamingo's sudden abdication...
King!
Your Majesty!
The people have been thrown in confusion.
Ring, ring, ring... ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
clank.